Do you see this viral photo?
Did you see this right here?
These kindergartners, they're best friends and they had twin day at school, so they wanted to dress alike on twin day.
And so here they are, please welcome Miles and Tanner and their moms, Brittany and Latina.
Okay, Brittany, what's the story behind the photo?
Well, it was Red Ribbon Week at school and it was twin day and so Miles really wanted to dress like Tanner and he was adamant that they looked identical and that they had the same hair and the same eyes, right?
He just, that's what he saw.
Yes, exactly.
We got the same eyes.
Same eyes, same hair.
All right, so what happened the next day at school?
Well, the night before I never heard of Tanner, I met Tanner.
Oh, you'd never met him?
No, and so I started stalking everyone in our town to try and find his mother, because I texted the teacher and she did give me Tanner's mother's name, just common courtesy, like I'm gonna send some clothes tomorrow for your kid to change into.
I need you to be on board with me, you know?
And so he did, so we sent the clothes to school and he went and changed as soon as he got there and then the teacher had sent us that picture, and the boys, and I was like, aww.
So you had no idea who Tanner was?
No, not at all.
You just bought the clothes because your boy came in and said, I got the dude at school, we got the same eyes, same hair, everything.
Hey, Tanner, Tanner, Tanner?
Yes.
Why is Miles your twin?
Because he wanna be my friend.
And Miles, why did you tell your mom that he was your twin?
Yeah, he was my best friend.
He's your best friend.
So y 'all twins, that's all that matters.
We're both five.
Huh?
Oh, you're both five?
Well, that, hell, that do it right there.
Oh my God.
Why do you think that many, LaKindra and Brittany, why do you think so many people love this story that it went viral?
I think in the media today, we see a lot of not the best stories, I guess you could say.
And so, okay.
You tripping.
Oh no, Kip.
You had no good story.
You tripping.
I think it just was a breath of fresh air for people to see something sweet and so innocent.
Let me ask y 'all something.
Have y 'all had a talk with them about it?
You haven't explained to them that that's.
No, but they act like they're brothers and they call themselves brothers, so we just.
Let it go.
Yeah.
Yeah, we're not gonna point out the differences.
That defeats the purpose.
Cause they don't see none.
That's right.
Because you know, so.
You know why?
Because kids don't see difference.
They're taught differences.
If you go to any playground, you see all the kids playing together.
You don't see until they get older, them separating.
That group over here eating.
That other group over there eating.
You don't see that.
Cause they get taught to them.
That's what.
If we could learn from kids, man.
Man, this world be a show cooler place, man.
This really, really, really, really.
Well, hey fellas, I wanna thank you for all of us, how to live.
I think that you two are the best friends.
I think you look just alike.
I love the fact that you're twins and y 'all should stay friends forever.
And have a good life.
And thank y 'all for coming.
Thank you.
Both of y 'all, thank you very much.